[Cairo]
[Luxor]
[Finally, WANGGEOZ arrive]
[at Giftun Island in Hurghada]
The title of this mission is…
"Conversations with the Ancients".
- "Conversations with the Ancients"
- "Conversations with the Ancients"?
[Find the ancient hieroglyphs]
[scattered all over the island]
Wow!
So this is it!
It's this kind of thing!
[Decoding the clues to collect the letters]
[and combining them into a complete word]
Eagle.
"A",
"M", "R"…
"C"!
[Bring the item that matches the word]
Did you bring it?
- Pencil.
- Incorrect!
Is it related to the word you found?
Where would you get that?
[Meanwhile, here are the letters revealed so far]
[A, L, M, R, C, E/Y]
[And]
[Appearing before Lee Teuk]
Wait, what's this?
[A suspicious Z]
This looks kinda fishy.
You have a "Z"?
- This one is that.
- What?
- To trick people…!
- Oh, you're trying to trick people.
[The fake Z Lee Teuk casually dropped]
1, 2, 3!
Nice!
[Engulfing WANGGEOZ in no time...]
Oh, "Z".
So, there's a "Z".
[Z???]
Oh? Oh?
There aren't many words with "Z" in them…
[They start chasing
an answer that doesn't exist]
[The chaos created by Lee Teuk's Z]
What's this? Wait, what was that?
[Today, the outcome will be revealed]
I really can't trust Lee Teuk! This is driving me nuts.
[Lee Teuk]
[Shin Dong]
[Dawn]
[Johnny]
[Kim Yo Han]
[Ji Sung]
I found 6!
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Then let's show
each other just one letter.
- One by one, okay.
- I have… 1, 2, 3, 4, 5...
[Shin Dong's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C]
Oh! I have 6 too.
[Lee Teuk's Collection Status: Z, A, EY, L, M]
Oh, okay then.
[Sharing everything after 20 years of trust]
Lee Teuk, then let's just open it.
Oh, just open it?
- Let's just open it completely together.
- Okay.
- 1, 2, 3!
[Lee Teuk's Collection Status: Z, A, EY, L, M, C]
[Shin Dong's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C, EY]
Oh, wait!
Lee Teuk, what's this?
Are you sure you have 6?
Isn't this one?
Lee Teuk, you have a "Z"?
- This one is that.
- What?
- To trick people…!
- Oh, you're trying to trick people.
[Lee Teuk's Collection Status: Z, A, EY, L, M, C]
This and this one are definitely real.
[Shin Dong's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C, EY]
Lee Teuk, you have everything I have!
You know less than I do!
Is there anything missing?
Hurry and look.
What's this? Was there an "E"?
"E" is this.
Yeah, so there is an "E"?
[CARAMEL]
Is it... "CARAMEL"?
Oh! Oh!
[Shin Dong's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C, EY]
[C, A, R, M, E, L]
If it's "CARAMEL",
there should be two "A"s, Lee Teuk.
Then it's not.
What item is there for a camel?
[Camel]
"Camel".
Oh!
- Lee Teuk, I think it's "CAMEL".
- Oh!
I've been looking for a camel
since earlier, and there are none!
[A little excited]
We're supposed to bring something related.
- Shin Dong.
- Yeah?
Don't you think it's "water"?
Camels store water here.
- Let's go quietly and try it out.
- Yeah.
[The two veterans
sneak around searching for water]
Shin Dong, did you find anything?
[Trying it out even if he gets nothing!]
I'm just gonna try it!
I'm not sure, but I'm gonna try it!
[For security, one person enters at a time]
Okay, please come in alone.
Step back, step back, please.
Please step back.
[Water]
Answer! "Water."
Please say it in English.
Water.
Incorrect.
Wait, really?
- It's not, it's not.
- It's not, it's not, it's not.
[Player substitution]
Oh, because...! Because…!
It's an empty bottle,
but pretend there's "water" in it.
[Super fail]
It's not?
- I think I'm starting to get this game.
- Oh, really?
So we're supposed to
find something related to this.
[Bring an item]
That completed word is here in this place.
[that's related to the completed word]
You have to bring that item here.
[What on earth is hidden on this island?]
Something related… Water.
Oh!
Wait! How am I supposed
to bring that over there?
You have to bring it here.
But I can't bring it here.
- Then, it must not be the answer.
- Oh! Here it is!
This!
A "cactus!"
What is that in English?
"Cactus"!
You must've combined
the letters together, no?
[Aloe]
Aloe.
["Cactus" is cactus]
Incorrect.
[A nice wrong answer]
Oh, it must be similar!
Oh! Camera?
This!
[Answer: "CAMERA"]
Please tell us.
A camera!
Shin Dong did the exact
same thing 10 minutes ago.
Ugh, Shin Dong!
[Booster up again]
[Basically a flying squirrel]
[Searching]
[DAWN's Collection Status: A, EY, L, Z]
Wait, that's…!
[Got the letter "C"!]
It's a different one! "C"!
[DAWN's Collection Status: A, EY, L, Z, C]
[Super Big Johnny appears between the parasols]
It's so tiring, right?
I'm seriously struggling.
[Here and there]
Wow, no way.
Of course, I couldn't find it
because it's placed like this!
[After Ji Sung looked at it earlier,]
[he hung it up in a rush and left]
[Found his 2nd hieroglyph, the bird]
A bird.
[Johnny's Collection Status: M, A]
[Decoded the bird image and got "A"]
Should I try to guess?
[PYRAMID]
From what I see, it's "PYRAMID".
I only saw "M" and "A," though.
[Johnny's Collection Status: M, A, C]
["C" obtained, so it's not "Pyramid"]
Wait, this is a "C".
"C", "M", "A".
Ji Sung! I think it's that.
[Sharing the good news he got from Lee Teuk]
But I actually know the letters, up to "Z"!
I know a few more letters.
[Tell me what got added]
Please share them.
If you share,
I'll quickly pass it along to you.
- There's a "Z"?
- There's apparently a "Z".
[Shin Dong's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C, EY]
I shared letters with Lee Teuk.
[Ji Sung's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C, Z]
He lied to you.
- Seriously?
- He lied.
Then, I think Lee Teuk
- is gonna traumatize me for life.
- He lied.
Wow, wait.
Ji Sung, you survived because of me!
There's no "Z".
So, what exactly
is this English word?
Camera... Isn't it "CAMERA"?
It's not "CAMERA".
What is it? "CARAMEL", maybe?
Ji Sung, did you get something wrong?
Like, the "C" or something?
Definitely not. I'm 100% sure about this.
There are many kinds of birds.
You could've gotten them confused.
Did you get the drawings correctly?
[3 bird drawings: A, M, W]
- I'm gonna double-check.
- Yeah.
I seriously have no clue.
At this time,
you'd think I would've found it.
But I'm bad at English.
What do I do?
Ji Sung, I have no idea at all.
- How many did you find?
- Me?
5!
You found a lot!
But I don't know English.
Yo Han, you're in
the same boat as me right now.
- I just can't piece it together.
[Frustrated]
[First, off to check the birds]
Ugh! I'm so tired!
[A groan involuntarily escapes]
Oh, I'm so tired.
There was something here earlier.
[3 bird drawings: A, M, W]
Yeah, it's this one.
This is… Let's look.
[This bird is definitely "A"]
It's "A". Yeah, yeah. It's "A", it's "A".
It's not "W".
It's not "A"… I mean, it's not "W".
I kept running! I kept searching!
I would find the letters,
then tell the members.
And then I'd ask them about it too.
That's when I realized
I was being way too honest.
I'm losing it.
This is driving me nuts.
[Fumbling]
Where the heck are my sunglasses?
[You're holding them in your hand...]
Oh, shoot. They're here.
[He begins begging the cameraman]
Can you please give me one little hint?
I seriously can't find it.
Just one…! The very first letter!
Oh, seriously! Please…!
[Q. What does English mean to Yo Han?]
I need to be reborn.
I should've quit sports sooner.
Yo Han, why did you
only do sports when you were little?
You should've studied English!
- Yo Han!
- Yes?
Let's team up!
Two heads are better than one.
Oh… I… I mean… The letters…
- How many did you find?
- I found 5.
I also have 5.
But I can't figure out
how to put them together.
Let's figure it out together.
[Shin Dong's target this time is Yo Han]
You might have some letters I don't.
I'll tell you right away.
[Shin Dong's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C, EY]
I have them like this.
Quickly sit down.
[Peeking]
It's better if we team up quickly.
[Yo Han's Collection Status: A, M, L, C, EY]
"A", "L"…
"M", "C"…
"C", "R"…
"Ey".
- There's a "Y"?
- "E" or "Y".
- There's either "E" or "Y"?
- Yes.
"E" or "Y".
[Double-checking "E/Y" with Lee Teuk and Yo Han]
I found this.
Really? Then it is 6 letters.
[If 6 are found, then the total letters are…]
Oh, but I'm not…
- I'm not good at English.
- Same here.
[The 2nd half of "Conversations with the Ancients"]
Geez, what could it be?
This is not easy.
I'm in big trouble.
[Announcement]
- A message just came from HQ.
- What did they say?
The total number of letters is 7.
There are 7 letters?
The total is 7 letters.
- 7 letters?
- Yes, 7 letters.
- What did you say?
- The total number of letters is 7.
- There are 7 letters?
- 7 letters?
[Ancient language = 7 letters]
Where did they all find them?
[Ji Sung found 5 letters]
Wait, hold on a sec.
[Shin Dong and Yo Han found 6 letters]
But since it's "E" or "Y",
couldn't both "E" and "Y" be included?
Is that how it goes?
[DAWN believes he has 5 letters, including Z]
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6.
[DAWN's Collection Status: A, EY, L, Z, C]
I have 6.
[Lee Teuk found 5 letters]
But where did they all find them?
[Lee Teuk's Collection Status: Z, A, EY, L, M, C]
I only found one.
[Johnny found the least]
"C", "M", "A". So that means there are 4 more.
[Current letter status]
[Tied for 1st: Shin Dong / Yo Han]
[Tied for 3rd: Lee Teuk / Ji Sung]
[5th: DAWN]
[6th: Johnny]
- Hey, Shin Dong.
- Yeah?
They said you and I both said the same answer.
[SUPER JUNIOR became one through "CAMERA"]
Oh, really?
- You did "CAMERA" too?
- Yeah.
(Camera...????)
This is so hard. I can't do this.
I have 6 letters,
but I can't piece them together.
It's so…
Are we too obsessed with that?
But don't they want us
to put the letters together?
Bring something?
Where is it?
Yeah, they want us to bring something.
I brought them 3 items,
and they were all wrong.
You took 3 items?
[Even after finding 6 out of the 7 letters]
Where could it be?
Should we just grab something and try?
[No idea...]
Ugh, where is it?
This doesn't feel right.
[Taking advantage
of the confusion...]
Oh, what? This…
[Shin Dong sneaks away]
Where is this?
[Suspicious]
Oh! You seem like
you're acting right now!
[Ignoring Yo Han's suspicion]
Oh! You seem like you're acting right now!
I think he found something.
But where is this?
[Entering HQ]
Answer! Ramesses?
You have to bring it here
Where is Ramesses?
If you can't bring it,
it's not the answer.
This is "Y" or "E", right?
Are both letters included?
It's one of the two.
One of the two.
[Shin Dong's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C, EY]
Oh, that's why it seemed so weird to me.
So it's one of the two…
[You got this, Captain Shin!]
Wow.
I really suck at English.
[It's a word chosen based on everyone's level…]
Just because your English isn't great
doesn't mean you can't solve it.
Can I please use AI just once?
[The one who uses modern civilization]
Then you will beg for eternity.
[will beg for eternity]
It's written on the first page.
I think I can beg
for the rest of my life...
Then, can I use it?
[Sacrificing his life for the status mission]
I want to beg forever.
Wanna know what's even funnier?
[Got all the letters from someone else]
I got these letters by making deals with everyone.
[Ultimate efficiency]
I haven't seen a single drawing yet.
[After gathering lots of info, he leaves HQ]
Sigh…
[Yo Han, who missed his chance to study English]
First, you gotta know what this is to find it.
[Yo Han's Collection Status: A, M, L, C, EY, R]
I don't know what it is,
so how am I supposed to find it?
Please give me your "CAMERA".
I'm gonna take the camera over.
[Remembered what the older members said earlier]
Please give me your camera.
[Camera]
Is it this?
Incorrect.
- It wasn't a camera.
- Please return it.
Sorry about that.
[The older members
even said they failed with it…]
[Deep in English anxiety]
I'm bad at English! What do I do about this?
[Meanwhile, Ji Sung]
(Still worried about the English)
[Ji Sung's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C, Z]
(Striding forward)
I…
Ca... camera...!
Camera!
[The 4th "CAMERA" challenger]
[From the very first "CAMERA" challenger,]
Camera!
[the members all connected with the same answer]
This!
- Please say the answer
- Camera!
- Did you bring it?
- Yes.
Incorrect.
Three people have already guessed "CAMERA".
- Really?
- Yes
There were 3 people smarter than me?
[Person smarter than Ji Sung #1]
Please give me one hint.
[Begging for a hint]
Just tell me the first letter.
You can't?
You're almost there.
I'm not there at all.
[Person smarter than Ji Sung #2]
Seriously, I'll give you 50,000 won!
[Offering a bribe]
Just one hint.
[Frustrated on both sides]
Combine them all together and bring it here.
I'm telling you, I can't combine them!
- Please go back.
- I can't combine them together.
Want to team up and try combining these with me?
Then that means someone scammed you.
I got scammed?
There's a high chance
you were scammed by someone.
[Dashing]
- Shin Dong!
- Yeah?
- I just went and checked.
We didn't find the letters ourselves,
but got them from the members, right?
They said there was a scammer!
The scammer was you, Lee Teuk.
- Oh, that's me?
- Yeah.
- Am I the only one?
- Yeah. The "Z".
[The one and only scammer, Lee Teuk]
So, it's you, Lee Teuk.
I went down there…
Oh, what's this?
This is suspicious.
- On the bed, there was a big "Z" written on it.
- Come on.
[The "Z" was written everywhere]
But it was written on all the beds there.
[First victim: DAWN]
1, 2, 3!
[Second victim: Ji Sung]
So to intentionally trick them,
[The confession diary of a scammer]
I found an "A", covered it up,
and then showed them one by one!
[Meanwhile, Lee Teuk's victims]
DAWN, I can't figure it out as I'm bad at English.
I think I found a lot of the letters, though.
Let's share, Ji Sung.
I've shared way too much.
Everyone probably knows already.
Oh, really?
- What should I do?
- Then, let's solve it together.
But one thing I don't trust is…
[Victim 1]
I traded one letter with Lee Teuk.
He might be lying.
[Victim 2]
I also swapped one with Lee Teuk.
[When suspicions turn into reality]
What did you trade?
Lee Teuk gave me "Z".
That's right.
- It must be a lie.
- I think it's weird.
[The "Z" just feels suspicious]
I don't know about this.
[Ji Sung's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C, Z]
I'll show you mine. These aren't it, but it's this.
- What? This?
- Yeah.
[DAWN's Collection Status: A, EY, L, Z, C]
I got this one.
[Ji Sung's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C, Z, EY]
The "E" is… Oh?
[DAWN's letters: A, EY, L, Z, C, M, R]
Oh, you didn't find this one!
[Got "E/Y"]
So it's "E" and "Y"?
Yeah. Wait a second.
I think we can actually do this.
[6 out of 7 letters is worth trying to figure out]
Ji Sung, let's make a plan.
Wait, from what I see here…
- What if…
- Prince, prince, prince! Pauper, pauper, pauper!
- 1, 2, 3, 4.
- Okay.
Since "A" is usually a vowel…
"A" and "E" are vowels.
Isn't it this?
"CAMEL"?
[Letter count doesn't match]
Isn't it this? "CAMEL"?
- Oh!
- Are we allowed to team up?
[Mr. John Jun Suh suddenly appears]
Are we allowed to team up?
(Has 3 letters)
[Happy to see his NCT member]
But Johnny!
- Johnny, but…
- Can we team up?
But, well…
Among the English words…
No, don't tell Johnny,
who's good at English.
That…
[The language barrier]
Johnny, but… Um… Wait.
[DAWN and Ji Sung are wary of Johnny]
I've got quite a few too.
- Okay, how many do you have?
- 4.
(Run)
(The lonely American)
Whenever I got close,
they all avoided me.
That hurt my feelings.
[JohnnyUS is destined to be lonely]
My youth is just slipping away again.
[Escaping from the predator]
Ji Sung.
["CAMEL"]
I'm pretty sure it's "CAMEL".
[Looks like a gathering of fools]
But I think we need to find a camel now.
I think it's right.
Should I try mimicking a camel?
[The correct answer has 7 letters]
["CAMEL" only has 5 letters]
Oh, it's 7 letters.
Then "Z" could actually be right.
I really can't trust Lee Teuk…
This is driving me crazy.
"Caramel"!!
Oh, never mind.
Sigh… Lee Teuk.
But if we exclude "Z"…
Let's just assume "Z" is correct.
No, I'm gonna ditch the "Z".
The letters spell "CAME…"
Do we fail if we're bad at English?
Yeah, no one's good at English here.
[A natural question pops up]
But Johnny speaks English, so why is he…?
(The lonely American)
This is really hard.
[Holds 3 letters: "M", "A", "C"]
They should've done this in Korean.
Even if we find it, what if
we don't know the English meaning?
[This word is very easy]
There's no way you don't know it.
Only "CARAMEL" comes to mind.
But where is there caramel here?
[Seems like they're almost there]
But it's not "CAMEL", right?
[But still going in circles]
It's not "CAMEL", because there are no camels!
I think a vowel is missing,
since there are 7 letters.
[Shin Dong's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C, EY]
We can just try adding vowels one by one.
[The last letter still conceals its identity]
I think someone mentioned "U" earlier.
"W".
"U".
"O".
DAWN, how many do you have?
[Tracking the unknown letter here too]
I've got 7 right now, but this…
They said there are 7 letters.
- You saw the bird, right?
- Yeah.
But the birds right now…
[There are 3 types of birds on the decoder]
There's "A" and "M",
and if you look here, there's one more.
Huh?
Are there one of each?
I mean... the animals?
There's one of each.
Why?
Then, I think there's a "W".
[The sudden appearance of a "W"]
"W"? Why?
- I think I saw both this and this.
- Oh, really?
I was like,
"These are the same,"
- and I remember skipping it.
- Wait, you saw it somewhere else?
Oh, what? They're the same.
[Skipped because
he had seen this bird before]
[Was the letter he missed "W"?]
Hey, then it must be "W".
- I think it's "W".
- Yo Han, seriously, the two of us…
[A wildcard has appeared]
Let's put our heads together.
Because over there,
there was an eagle somewhere in there.
[The "A" eagle Yo Han mentioned is correct]
Wow! This is bad!
I'm in big trouble!
I saw a similar bird over there again.
So I was like, "What? It's the same,"
and I skipped it.
From what I can see,
it might not be the owl for "M".
You have an "M", right??
There's definitely an owl "M".
[He spotted the owl "M" too]
- I saw the owl for sure.
- Where'd you see the owl?
Where was it again...
- Then did you see three birds?
- Yes.
Then we have 8 letters.
[Chaos ensues with the appearance of "W"]
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
[Where did it all go wrong?]
We found a wrong clue somewhere.
[Chapter. 7 God hides His secrets
within the weakest of His creatures]
[Meanwhile, Johnny]
Let's go again!
[Johnny's Collection Status: M, A, C]
Let's start over from the beginning.
Oh!
[Heading out to find the last 3 letters]
"M", "A", "C", "R".
[Johnny's Collection Status: M, A, C, R]
[He searches]
I don't think I checked here yet.
[And searches again]
Oh, it was a nail.
[And searches some more]
Ugh…
[Found a hut beyond the fence]
[This hut is…]
[This is where Yo Han, DAWN, and Lee Teuk…]
Wow! This is bad! I'm in big trouble!
[first found the ancient language early in the mission]
It's here!
It's this!
It's this kind of thing!
[Just like the 3 who came before,]
[Johnny heads inside the fence]
Oh, it's here.
[Found the "A"]
[Johnny's Collection Status: M, A, C, R, A]
Wait, I already had this?
Two "A"s…
[There were two "A"s from the start]
[The 7 letters of
the ancients have been revealed]
[When you decode
the 7 letters and combine them]
[Aacelmr]
[Caramel]
[The answer is "CARAMEL"]
[Actually, since earlier,]
Only "CARAMEL" comes to mind.
"Caramel".
[the members have been shouting "CARAMEL"]
Is it "CARAMEL"?
[But the fact that there are two "A"s…]
There should be two "A"s, Lee Teuk.
Then it's not.
Oh, what? They're the same.
[…is something no one realized]
I realized that there are two "A"s.
[The first to realize there are two "A"s]
If this is an "A",
it's either the first
or the second one, right?
[The lonely Chicago guy suddenly rises]
"MAC"… "MAC"…
[Who will find the caramel hidden in this place]
"The one who finds and understands the ancient language"
"will become a prince."
[and bring it to "the highest hut"]
"Blessings await those"
[to become the two princes?]
"who bring 'that' to the highest hut."
Johnny.
- Johnny, can I just team up with you?
- Huh?
Can I just team up with you?
Do you want to?
[After many twists, the NCT alliance is formed]
I got 5 letters.
- How many do you have?
- For now…
[Johnny's Collection Status: M, A, C, R, A]
"E" or "Y".
[Ji Sung's Collection Status: A, L, M, R, C, Z, EY]
What's "E or Y"?
There are both letters.
If you look here, there's "E" and "Y".
Oh, okay. "E".
- "A".
[The letters Ji Sung ran around to find]
"L".
[Taking them all]
- "M".
- "R".
- "C".
- But, I have 2 "A"s.
- What Lee Teuk told me was…
- There are two "A"s?
- Yeah.
[Sharing the most important info]
But that's the owl…
- There are two "A"s?
- Yeah.
Did I see it wrongly?
This is really crucial.
Because the "A" was here.
- The "A" was here?
- Yeah.
Then, there are two "A"s!
- There are two "A"s! There are two!
- Right?
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
It's definitely "A".
[Finally, Z is out]
Lee Teuk was really lying!
[Johnny and Ji Sung collected all 7 letters]
[Current letters secured]
[Tied for 1st: Johnny, Ji Sung]
[Tied for 3rd: Shin Dong, DAWN, Yo Han]
[Last place: Lee Teuk]
"Caramely"?
"Caramel"?
[He shouted the answer!]
"A", "A", "C", "R"…
[But no one noticed]
Okay, let's go sit down and figure this out.
[Will they find the answer "CARAMEL"?]
The "A" was right here.
- This was the "A".
- There was an "A" there too.
- Yeah, exactly! Okay, okay!
- There was an "A" there, too.
We found them all.
[DAWN spots the NCT alliance]
How many did you find?
We found all of them just now.
[Ji Sung is giving it away again]
I think we know everything.
The numbers… I mean, we know the spelling.
- But we're can't combine them together right now.
- Really?
[While DAWN and Ji Sung resent Lee Teuk]
Honestly, right now, Lee Teuk…
- Lee Teuk is driving me crazy.
- Oh, I really can't trust Lee Teuk.
[Johnny drifts off alone]
"CARAMELY"? Is there a word like "CARAMELY"?
[Johnny's Collection Status: M, A, C, R, A, EY, L]
I can't trust anyone anymore!
This is no good! I need to go find them myself!
[He just needs to create "CARAMEL"]
[Did he realize it?!]
Oh!
I gotta go to Johnny.
Johnny!
Oh, it's wrong.
- I thought it was "CALAMARI", like squid
- Johnny.
- How many did you find?
- All of them.
- You found them all?
- Yeah.
I have 5.
I can't figure it out.
[On guard]
So?
No, just look at this right now.
[Lee Teuk trying to leech off info]
You're good at English.
So, I'm just curious.
- About what?
- Can you combine these letters?
Not yet.
- It's not, right?
- Yeah.
That means someone lied.
- From what I can tell...
- Yeah?
You lied.
It's not me.
The "Z" you told Ji Sung
about was a lie, right?
That's one I found
by mistake from the start.
Oh, as expected.
No, so basically…
Let's figure it out together.
[Finally gets to the point]
I tried combining them so many times now.
[Glances]
Since you're good at English…
Yeah.
But from what I think…
[Distracting him with conversation]
Yeah?
Yeah.
- But from what I think…
- Yeah?
[Successfully peeked]
Being good at English
doesn't mean you'll get it right.
Oh, really?
(Pretending like he didn't look)
You have the same ones I do!
Take a look!
Why won't you believe me?
These are the ones I got running around at first.
[With his smooth talk,]
It's similar.
[he has Johnny completely fooled]
That's true.
(Sneaking peeks till the very end)
This is the key point.
[Johnny, your notebook has
been completely exposed…]
[Just suffocating]
[CARAMEL]
I got it.
[Johnny figured out "CARAMEL" as the answer]
[Following closely]
[Now, he has to find the caramel]
I'm just going my own way.
[Desperate]
Let's do it together.
Please, Johnny.
Let's team up.
[So, where can he find the caramel?]
But I have no idea where I'm supposed to find it.
Exactly, tell me so I can help you.
This feels so refreshing.
- You know what it is?
- Yeah.
Let's share it.
[The hyenas surround Johnny]
Oh, guys. But what are you gonna do?
You should've been quiet about this!
I'm the only one who knows right now.
(Just tell me)
What are you gonna do?
If that's the case,
don't tell anyone else.
- Don't share with anyone.
- Yeah, I won't.
Let's share it! Wait, come over here.
Oh, wait! Come here for a second.
[Lee Teuk feels frustrated not knowing the answer]
Oh, this seriously feels so refreshing right now.
- What?
- Let's find it together.
It's 7 letters.
[So what's the combo?]
I know it's 7 letters.
I should've been born in the US too.
- But…
- Yeah?
[Shin Dong approaches again]
I'll tell you, Lee Teuk…
- No, no, no. Let me tell you.
- Yeah.
- Is it "CARAMEL" or not?
- Oh, really?
[Shin Dong figured out the answer too]
Is it or is it not? From what you know.
[Now Shin Dong and Johnny
are the ones who know the answer]
- Yeah.
- Yeah, okay.
- What? Do you two know?
- Did you figure it out?
- So where is that exactly?
- Hey!
- Let me in on it too!
- I have no clue.
- How'd you find it?
- I have no idea, Lee Teuk.
- How'd you combine it?
- I said I don't know.
[Pouting]
[On the move to find caramel]
Have you gone this way, Shin Dong?
But there are no cameras over here.
But the cameras are following us…
[They head to the minibar…]
[Looks like a dead end]
I don't think it's this way.
[Lee Teuk, who was following, also stops]
Where is it exactly?
(Pretending to combine the letters)
[Just then, his NCT ally passes by]
Ji Sung.
[Everyone reacts]
Yes?
Did you find it?
(Come here)
[Following closely]
[Spotted the crew tagging along]
Johnny!
I'll help you find it!
I'm good at finding stuff.
Did you find it?
I figured it out.
- Really?!
- Yeah.
- What is it?
- Why? Why? Why?
[Ji Sung shared a lot with Johnny]
But I shared everything with him.
So, I'll tell you, Ji Sung.
- You can't do that.
- Why not?
[Unreasonable]
Ji Sung doesn't know either.
Oh, he told me the number.
We need to have an NCT meeting.
It's "CARAMEL".
Got it?
- Is it really that?
- Yeah.
[Find it quickly, Ji Sung]
But Shin Dong knows it too.
That's actually what
we did in the beginning!
We need to find the caramel.
Yeah, but how do we find it?
[Hop]
Excuse me, sir.
By any chance…
Do you… Do you have "CARAMEL"?
- Caramel?
- Yes.
[Lee Teuk trails closely again]
Do you… Do you have "CARAMEL"?
- Caramel?
- Yeah.
Caramel, caramel.
[He heard "CARAMEL"!]
["CARAMEL" reaches Lee Teuk's ears]
[4 people know the answer]
[But there are only two spots]
The prince status will be given to only two people.
[No one knows where the caramel is]
Please say it's correct.
Oh, but I think it's right.
He's caught on, he's caught on!
[Who will get to be the prince?!]
Where could it be?
By any chance, do you have caramel?
[Candidate Johnny visits the restaurant]
[Cautious]
Do you have "CARAMEL"?
[No idea]
No? No caramel? No?
[Candidate Shin Dong does a staff body check]
Director, got anything in your pockets?
[Is he a troublemaker or what…?]
Do you have it or not?
Director, you don't have anything?
[Shin Dong trudges along]
It's gotta be here somewhere.
[and even checks inside the accommodation]
What's crazy about my gut feeling is…
I just wanted to try opening up
the window at our accommodation.
[Something came to mind as he opened the door]
When I got close and tried opening it, it opened.
Then something flashed through my mind.
When we first went upstairs
to check the rooms,
I remembered there was
a mounted camera by the stairs.
If that's still recording,
the answer's gotta be
in the accommodation.
[Checking the camera]
Oh? It's still rolling!
[Will Shin Dong's gut feeling turn out right?]
[Found the caramel]
[Caramel found, thanks to
this entertainer's gut feeling]
[Sprinting]
[Setting a new personal record for speed]
[He brings the "CARAMEL" to the "highest hut"]
Did you find it?
I was searching for ages
to find where it was!
Please give it to me.
Caramel.
Shin Dong, you are today's first prince.
[Shin Dong confirmed as a prince]
I'm the prince!
I got the answer
using the letters Ji Sung gave me,
and I found it after
Johnny gave me confirmation.
I've never seen the "ancient language".
I never cross-checked it, not even once.
Yet, I became the first prince.
- I'm the prince!
- Oh, come on!
Why is Shin Dong so good at games?
I'm the prince!
Seriously?
Where is it... Shin Dong,
where did you get it from?
[Arrived at the restaurant Johnny checked earlier]
Is it not here? Doesn't it feel like it should?
Excuse me!
Do you have caramel?
[No idea]
No?
[The struggle to find caramel]
Only one spot, only one spot.
I really don't want
to play the next game!
[Spotted caramel syrup at the bar]
This… uh…
(Please)
Sir.
Just one minute, just one minute
- We can't.
- Really?
[Desperate plan fails]
30… 30 seconds!
I run fast! Oh my god!
Trururururu!
[Please]
Please, please!
[How much will it take?]
How much?
Oh, what do I do…?
Shin Dong! Can you just tell me
the first letter? Shin Dong!
I'll tell you what it's not. Call it out!
"E", "A", "L",
"M", "R", "Z"…
Definitely not "Z".
[Now, everyone knows about the fake "Z"]
You guys got totally played by the "Z".
- The "Z" was Lee Teuk's decoy.
- Ugh! Lee Teuk! Lee Teuk!
- Lee Teuk was lying.
- It's a lie, huh?
I'm telling you it's right!
Yo Han, hurry up...
No, it's every man for himself now.
It's every man for himself now.
[Who will be the last prince?!]
I just need to find it.
I think I got it.
[Just then, Lee Teuk comes running]
I'm…!
[Johnny sprints too!]
[Johnny arrives first]
I'm…!
Oh, what?
[Will the game end just like this?]
I guess it's over.
It's over.
I just wanna see if it's right… Is it right?
No… This is a lie.
Johnny.
You are the second prince!
I'm…!
[Johnny confirmed as prince]
The prince!
Yeah!!!
[3 minutes ago]
I haven't checked this place yet.
[Start searching the unchecked
prince's accommodation]
Before going up to the restaurant,
I asked the staff.
"Can we go anywhere? Even the restaurant?"
They said "Yes," and that's when I knew.
Then I need to check this place,
and that place as well.
I'm really bad at treasure hunts.
That's really a fact.
This is the first time
in my life I've won one.
I'm not usually
the type to shout like that.
- I guess I can shout too.
- I'm the prince!
It felt amazing.
Yeah!!
Hey, where did you find it?
- Wow!
- Hey, where did you find it?
I'm the prince!
[Walking toward the shout of the prince,]
[Ji Sung falls to his knees]
[Honestly, Ji Sung...]
"Caramel".
[He said the answer
just 10 minutes into the mission]
Oh, "CARAMEL"?
[He kept saying "CARAMEL" many times after that]
Is it "CARAMEL"?
"Caramel". "Caramel"?
"Caramel"? "Caramel".
What worries me is
if the answer's already been revealed
and I don't know what it is,
it'd be kind of embarrassing.
[Embarrassed Ji Sung,]
Today, I really have to…
[who really wanted to be a prince]
I really have to become a prince.
I really want to be a prince.
- Ugh.
- Wow!
[1st Pauper status]
Whether it made me look good or bad,
[Even set aside his image]
I was so determined to become a prince.
[What he got back was his 2nd Pauper status]
Ugh, this is so unfair!
[The world's first double pauper]
The world's first to be a pauper twice in a row.
[After getting his 3rd Pauper status in a row]
A woodpecker on the left, and a club on the right.
[He achieved his 4th Pauper status]
[Basically ALL Pauper status]
I'm actually achieving this epic feat.
I didn't choose to be a pauper
because I wanted to be one.
I worked so hard, but ended up a pauper.
I couldn't believe it for like 5, 10 minutes.
[Lee Teuk confirmed as a pauper]
I'm…! I'm the pauper!
I thought I had it,
but when it didn't happen,
it just stopped being fun.
All the princes have been decided.
DAWN! You're a pauper!
Yo Han's the physical member, right?
I thought about coaxing Yo Han
and taking his letters.
[Picked the wrong target]
But Yo Han gave me wrong information too.
The main reason I lost was that I misread him.
- DAWN, you're a pauper!
- No, no!
Why aren't you saying it
to Yo Han and only to me?
Yo Han, you are a pauper too.
What the heck.
[Shin Dong: Prince 3, Pauper 1]
[Johnny: Prince 2, Pauper 2]
[DAWN: Prince 3, Pauper 1]
[Yo Han: Prince 1, Pauper 3]
[Lee Teuk: Prince 2, Pauper 2]
[Ji Sung: Prince 0, Pauper 4]
[Disappointed]
It's all over.
Oh, but I really could've done that…!
I thought there was something
if I finished drinking the mango juice.
[Gave himself an extra mission]
So you drank it all?
I drank all of this!
Yo Han, you should've
teamed up with me.
I thought the mission
was to finish the mango juice.
[A fitting remark for someone who lost]
That's why I drank all the mango juice!
- Was that left for us to drink?
- Yes.
But you don't know
how long that juice was out there.
We left it for you
to drink in case you got tired.
- Oh!
- Oh, really?
No wonder it kept appearing.
I almost drank them all.
The correct answer was this.
[The caramel they had been searching for]
Where was this?
- In the room.
- It was in the room.
[Bummer]
Room 1 and Room 4 had them.
- Here, take one each.
- I'm not eating it.
I don't want to eat it.
(Into my mouth then)
Today's princes are Shin Dong and Johnny.
[Shin Dong and Johnny
confirmed as the 4th princes]
[Shin Dong, Johnny, the 4th princes are born]
[Without finding a single clue,]
It looked like Shin Dong didn't do any legwork,
[Shin Dong became a prince]
but found it anyway.
That's the wisdom of life.
I told him too much!
But Ji Sung is really kind,
[Ji Sung gives generously]
because he told us everything!
I was like, "Ji Sung, let's share."
He told me all of his letters
and then ran off!
- What?
- Huh??
- Right, director? Right?
- Hey, what?
- You're an angel!
- When… When was that?
Hey, did you not need mine?
- When I saw you in the beginning…
- No, it's not that…
I don't really remember this, but…
I was really busy.
I was so focused on finding it no matter what,
so I was really busy.
And so,
[DAWN's first time being a pauper]
our DAWN's streak
- of being a prince is broken.
- Oh, finally!
- But…!
- Ji Sung…
[Ji Sung achieves ALL Pauper status]
Ji Sung's streak of being a pauper continues!
Wow, this is amazing.
Pauper, pauper, pauper, pauper.
- Ji Sung's energy is on another level.
- This game was hard.
[Pauper Ji Sung, Season 2 confirmed]
Ji Sung's locked in for Season 2.
Will Ji Sung stay a pauper again in Season 2?
- Alright, good job, everyone.
- Yes.
- In a bit…
- I was so close…!
we will begin the prince's pool party,
attended by the paupers.
- Wow, that's awesome!
- Then, what do we do?
Attended… We're attending to them?
- Then you gotta wait outside with towels.
- Yes, like bring towels and drinks.
[His first pauper run is a tough one]
Wow, nice.
[With the paupers attending to them,]
This is nice, being a prince on the last day!
[the princes' pool party begins]
Ji Sung, let's look forward to Season 2.
- Your Highnesses, you must be tired.
- Yes.
Instead of swimming,
how about going in and resting?
[Ignoring]
This is so nice.
[The princes casually take a seat]
Oh, princes, please have a seat.
Our paupers…!
Oh, you're all dressed nicely today.
[Flattery Mode ON]
Oh, our prince!
This is nice. I love this kind of thing.
Prince!
[Satisfied]
I'm into things like this.
- Oh, you're really tense!
- Yeah.
You're really tense here.
[Human fan ON]
- Oh my.
- This is so nice.
Alright, first things first!
When you come to
a place like this for vacation,
resting is all well and nice,
but I'm craving something refreshing.
Something refreshing! Watermelon juice!
The four of you play Rock-Paper-Scissors.
- Play Rock-Paper-Scissors…
- Rock-Paper-Scissors?
And the one who loses!
- Just one person?
- Yes, just one person
[Bring the drinks]
will go and grab the drinks.
[Whining]
You should've said something sooner...
I just thought of it.
- Oh, you just thought of it now?
- Yeah, it just came to me.
- Yeah, it's a bit far.
- Alright.
Being a prince means having power.
[Ready to enjoy it fully]
I gotta use it a lot at times like this.
[Pure joy]
Honestly, it was pure bliss for us.
- And everyone.
- Yes?
I thought telling you this early on
would make you work harder.
We'll pick the best pauper.
We've prepared a big gift!
[Intrigued]
What is it? What?
[Best Pauper Awards]
Could it be a room?
You're giving us a room?
[What's the perk of being the Best Pauper?]
It's a surprise gift, everyone.
- So, you gotta work hard, okay?
- Oh, tell us what it is! I'm curious!
[What on earth is it?]
Can't you tell us?
Are we moving up in status?
[To be revealed shortly]
After we've checked, I'll tell you.
Okay, okay.
[Resuming the drink errand bet]
The loser of Rock-Paper-Scissors.
Is the loser going?
- The loser.
- Yes.
If you just want to go, you can.
[Lee Teuk and Yo Han will go]
I'll go and come back!
- I'll go!
- Anyone who wants to go can go.
[Are we really going?]
We'll just play Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Since it's the first one and all.
- I love your enthusiasm!
- Yes, alright.
Okay, everyone.
- It's too obvious for the loser to go, so…
- The 1st-place winner?
[The 2nd-place winner will go]
2nd place will go!
- The 2nd-place winner will go.
- I like things like this.
So, 2nd place will go.
Shoot or 1st place!
[Scissors / Rock / Scissors / Paper]
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Rock / Scissors / Paper / Scissors]
[Paper / Paper / Rock / Paper]
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Last place Ji Sung is excluded]
Okay, last place, step out!
[The 2nd-place winner among the three goes]
So, 2nd place among you three.
Shoot or 3rd place!
[Scissors / Rock / Scissors]
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
- Okay!
- Oh!
[DAWN excluded]
The winner between you two will go.
- Lee Teuk, it's because we said we'd go!
- We said we'd go…!
Shoot or win!
[Rock / Scissors]
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Yo Han wins]
Sweet!
- Off you go!
- Oh, nice, nice!
Nice! Oh, what do you want?
[I'll take your orders, Your Highnesses]
An iced Americano with extra ice.
And a Coke Zero with ice.
Pauper! Can you get us some too?
[Okay, got it]
Okay! I'm feeling generous! What do you want?
- I'll have a Coke.
- A Coke.
- Zero!
- A Coke Zero.
- I want a Coke too!
- A Coke.
Two regular Cokes,
Two Coke Zeros, an Iced Americano.
- One with lots of ice, please.
- Oh, I'll take a Coke Zero too.
[Orders start flooding in]
Three Coke Zeros…
- A regular Coke.
- One regular Coke.
- Ice, ice!
- Ice…
Why are you being like this, Lee Teuk?
[We were gonna go together earlier…]
Lee Teuk, we were supposed to do it together.
- Is it heavy?
- Yeah, carrying five is kinda tough.
- Oh, really? Shall we go together?
- Let's go together then.
Go on ahead.
Do you want one more person?
Because I might drop something on the way.
I have to carry them
with both hands like this.
[Alright, send one more pauper!]
Okay, the three of you
will play Rock-Paper-Scissors again.
Who's going?
[The 2nd-place winner again]
2nd place will go. 2nd place!
- Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Rock / Paper / Scissors]
[Let's go together, Lee Teuk...!]
Lee Teuk! Lee Teuk!
[Scissors / Scissors / Rock]
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
- Ugh!
- Oh!
[Lee Teuk excluded]
Lee Teuk, step out.
[DAWN VS Ji Sung]
Shoot or win!
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Scissors / Rock]
[Ji Sung wins]
Oh, Ji Sung!
- I was happy because I won.
- Sorry.
[The youngest paupers gets the drinks]
Something is going on between us.
- I was happy I won.
- Let's go.
Have a good trip!
- It's us again?
- I know, right?
- There's a problem with this!
- It's us again.
I'm used to it.
I have nothing to lose.
[Enlightenment]
But I've gotten used to it too.
- Hey, you two, take a seat.
- Oh, can we sit here?
- Please sit for a moment. Yes.
- Thank you, Your Highness.
- Please sit for a moment.
- Your Highness.
[Ahead of the real fun by the pool]
Yes, we…
Firstly, Lee Teuk, I'm sorry,
but can you check the water temperature?
Yeah, tell us how the water is.
- Lee Teuk! You're quite funny!
- Oh, was it funny?
[Scored 1 point for the slapstick]
Plus 1 point!
- When you head down…
- Oh, that was funny!
- Be careful going down.
- Oh, that was funny.
- It's slippery.
- That was funny.
It's slippery.
Wow, I didn't realize
this would be so funny, then…
DAWN, please check
the water temperature too!
- How funny will he be?
- It's colder than expected.
[Check the temperature again...??]
It's colder than expected.
[LOL]
You have to really check the water temperature, okay?
[Thermometer DAWN is on the move]
I'll check the water temperature now.
- Yes, the water temperature.
- Sirs.
- The water temperature.
- I didn't know you were good at slapstick too.
Sorry, but...
- DAWN.
- Yes?
Your legs are so thin.
Hey, I found someone
with skinnier legs than mine!
[The fallen prince's legs]
They look like ostrich legs!
I might get blown away!
Let's check the water temperature again.
[Hesitating]
The water temperature?
- Yes, check the water temperature.
- I'm worried he might get blown away!
[Reading the room]
Please check the water temperature.
No, but seriously…
I have to… I have to be funny, right?
If you're funny, that's extra points.
If you're funny…!
If you're funny, yes, yes.
[Determined to be funny]
- I'll check the temperature, Your Highnesses.
- Please check the water temperature.
[Temperature check]
[Nice one, DAWN]
Wow, that was good!
- Wow, that was good!
- Oh, totally, totally!
- How's the water temperature?
- The water temperature is perfect.
Hey, I wasn't expecting that!
- How's the water temperature?
- It's just right.
- It's just right?
- Isn't it a little cold?
- It's good to go in?
- You can go in.
[The struggles of the former ALL Prince]
We'll go in after our drinks.
- Oh, after your drinks.
- Yes, yes.
- Did I get any bonus points?
- 2 points!!
- I'll give you 2 points!
- Agreed, agreed!
- Aw! Me too! Me too!
- I'll give you 2 points.
[The princes couldn't be more pleased]
But let's make them all do this!
Oh, that was fun!
Oh, it was perfect.
[Lamenting his fate]
Why couldn't I find the caramel?
[The youngest paupers arrive at the minibar]
Excuse me.
[Drink order list]
Zero Coke…
[Four Zero Cokes]
1, 2, 3, 4.
Four Zero Cokes.
- Four?
- Yeah.
[One Coke]
One Coke with ice.
[One Iced Americano]
And one iced Americano with ice.
(Lots of ice)
But the iced Americano is full ice, please.
[Ordered with lots of ice, without forgetting]
Thank you!
You two, for 2 points, race there and back.
Let's see who's faster.
- Are you a good swimmer??
- I can't swim at all.
- Oh, not at all?
- Yeah.
You can just walk it.
- As long as you make it somehow.
- Yes, yes.
[Whining]
But it's really cold.
If you whine about the cold,
that's minus points.
No, like…
[Whining...]
We could freeze to death...
- Lee Teuk.
- Yes?
[Backing down]
Okay, okay, got it, got it.
Don't say my name like that…
- I know I'm Lee Teuk.
- Okay, I'm ready.
[Stop whining and prepare for the swim battle]
Let's go!
Do you have a whistle?
[Proactive since it's the prince's command]
Can you blow it once? You don't have one?
- Oh, it's cold!
- The shot looks nice!
- Black and white looks great!
- Yeah.
[Go stone vibes]
You look like Go stones.
So cold!
Ugh! So cold!
[Whining overload]
It's so cold!
Is he sneezing?
[Calm down and come back]
Okay, you two, come this way, and we'll begin.
Hey, it's way too deep here!!!!
Try going in once to see how deep it is.
- Wait a second.
- Yeah?
[Getting emotional]
We're paupers, but not slaves.
- Then, you're not gonna do it?
- No, I will, but…
- You don't have to do it.
- Lee Teuk! - 10 points!
- No, no, wait, wait!
Let's talk for a second!
No, no, no. I'll do it.
(Desperate)
No, I'll do it, I'll do it.
Alright, here we go! Ready!
- Not yet, not yet!
- Stay at the end, at the end!
Now, ready!
Wait, hold on!
There's something here!
- Ready!!
- Wait!
Go!
[The round-trip race begins]
Alright, it's starting!
[They jump into
the water at the same time]
- Oh! Oh!
- They're swimming!
Oh, they're swimming!
They're both great swimmers.
Hold on.
The princes are out of the pool,
and the paupers are swimming…?
[What is going on??]
This is seriously hilarious.
They must've been
told to do something.
[The paupers are having a blast swimming]
You gotta go all the way!
[Giggles]
[Advancing toward the finish line]
[Pauper Lee Teuk is in the lead]
(Giving up)
Oh, who will it be?
[Pauper Lee Teuk arrives]
The winner is…!
[Lee Teuk wins]
Lee Teuk!!
Wow, nice!
Your drinks are here!
- Oh, the drinks are here! The drinks.
- Yes.
Come out and have a drink.
[Jealous]
It was actually better to go there instead.
Oh, really?
[What happened, Lee Teuk?]
This…
This is the ice water…
[Crawling...]
The Zero Cola with ice. Thank you.
- Your Highness, would you like a straw?
- Oh, I'm good…
[Touchy]
Are you asking if I eat straws?
- You said, "Would you like a straw?"
- I meant with a straw! With a straw!
[Do I look like I'd eat the straw too?]
I don't eat straws.
[That's rude]
Even though I look like I'd inhale everything.
No, no!
So, these two here
[DAWN and Lee Teuk scored +2 points]
each got 2 points.
Oh, for what reason?
[MAKNAEZ questionably have 0 points]
You guys still have 0 points.
For what reason?
They checked the water temperature
in a very entertaining way.
So we gave them 2 points
for being funny.
- How did they check the temperature in a fun way?
- How did they make it fun?
Sigh… Just do it first.
Look at how Lee Teuk looks.
Wow, how do you even make this fun?
We'll start the water temperature check
with Pauper Ji Sung first!
[Massive pressure]
Why do I feel so burdened about this?
I just have to check
the water temperature.
Wait, wait. Okay, okay!
[Okay, okay]
Like this? This kind of vibe?
[Candidate 1. Ji Sung]
Ooh! Wow!
Are you ready to check
the water temperature?
Ready!
Go!
[The way he came out is funny]
The writers in the front were like, "Wow!"
- What do you think?
- It's a bit disappointing…
- But, I mean…
- The idea!
- The idea wasn't bad.
- The idea, the idea.
- I overdid it…
- You should've said something!
I overdid it…
- He said he overdid it.
- You should've said something.
- For that, I'll give you 1 point.
- Yes, Ji Sung gets 1 point!
- It's so cold.
[The physical comedy specialist steps up]
But we have Yo Han, right?
[Candidate #2. Yo Han]
Yo Han, you ready?
Yes, yes.
Yes, I'm ready!
You're ready? Then, get ready!
Water temperature check! Go!
First, I'm gonna wet my chest
before going in.
- I'll splash some water on myself and go in.
- Yes.
That's totally fine.
[The "water temperature" (mul-on-do) is]
It's "utopia"! (Mureung-dowon)
[So hilarious]
That was funny! Wow, so fun…!
[Yo Han scores 3 points]
Yo Han, 3 points for you!
Oh! Me too! Me too!
[Requesting a joint score]
Oh, I give you 3 points. 3 points!
[The full story behind their combo play]
That was a good assist.
- 0.5 points! 0.5 points!
- Oh!
Without goggles!
[Whisper]
Lee Teuk, can you kick me from the back?
- Yo Han, you ready?
- When you say, "I'll check the water temperature", then…
(Strategy meeting)
[Sneaking up quietly]
That's totally fine.
[Kicking him over]
[What is this teamwork?]
[+3 points]
Thank you, Lee Teuk.
[An iconic scene created by staging]
They staged it. They planned it together.
"Can you kick me from behind?"
They staged it. They planned it.
[Whining for more points]
Hey, give me 0.5 points! I helped plan it!
[Scoring factor: Utopia]
"Utopia" was really good. "Utopia".
"Utopia" was really great.
- Oh, that's what you liked?
- Yeah, "Utopia".
Was the kick not that great?
That was just being a bad person.
[Whining till the end]
Why are you being like that!
"Utopia" was great.
Why are you being mean!
The swimming match between these two was fun.
Do you two wanna have a swimming match?
[Swimming match: Yo Han VS Ji Sung]
- A swimming match? - To the end and back.
We did a quick race, and it was really fun.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
- Can you swim, Yo Han?
- Swim? Oh, of course.
These two just walked.
- Oh, they walked?
- Yeah.
[Let's just give it a shot]
Okay, you two get ready.
We'll put 2 points on the line!
2 points on the line!
[It didn't seem too bad earlier]
Being a pauper doesn't seem too bad…
- Alright, ready!
- Okay, okay.
Go!
[Getting kicked in again]
[Starting at a similar pace]
They're off!
[Sudden intense swimming]
Oh! He's good! Oh!
He pretended he couldn't swim!
[Amazed]
Whoa! Why is he so good at this?
- Wow, it's really deep!
- Right?
[No difference despite his swimming skills]
Hey, come here! You gotta come back!
Ji Sung!
[Can't miss out on 2 points]
Oh, wow!
- He's really cool.
- Yo Han's good at swimming.
- What's going on?
- What? What's happening?
[Cough]
[A true variety show genius]
[What is the result of the walking match?]
- Yo Han wins!
- Oh!
He's good!
Yo Han's comfortable in the water.
[Scored 5 points from the water alone]
Yo Han already has 5 points! If this keeps up…
Ji Sung, you okay?
- I don't get along with water.
- I see.
I kicked him again this time.
Please give him a towel.
- Do you want minus points?
- No, no.
[The partner feels wronged]
No, like, I did this!
You look really cold right now.
- Yes, I'm really cold.
- Do you want me to warm you up?
We should keep Lee Teuk warm too!
I think a hot bowl
of ramyeon would do the trick.
- Ramyeon?
- Yep
Wow, eating ramyeon right now…!
[A team battle over ramyeon prep]
Alright, we'll have a team battle.
- Oh, a team battle.
- Please form your teams.
[Flipping palms to decide teams]
Let's play Up or Down.
- Please form your teams.
- Yes.
Up or Down!
[Palm Up / Palm Down]
[Palm Down / Palm Up]
[Yo Han and Lee Teuk become a team]
Okay.
[DAWN and Ji Sung become a team]
Okay, it's two against two!
We'll play the Palm Push game!
The Palm Push game.
[Sensing victory]
I feel like Yo Han will be good at this!
[And one person suddenly gets quiet…]
We'll play the Palm Push game.
- The winner keeps playing.
- It's okay. You can do it.
The winner keeps going.
[What are you saying?]
Yo Han, you can beat them all, right?
- You can beat them all, right?
- By myself?
I've never won this game even once.
Oh, really?
[Which team will win?]
The losing team will make the ramyeon,
and the winning team will eat it with us.
Sounds good.
[Round 1]
Everyone, bring your legs closer.
[Yo Han VS Ji Sung]
Put your feet completely together, please. Ready!
- I'll catch you from behind just in case.
- Yeah, just in case.
Ready!
Go!
[Trouble right from the start]
[Meanwhile, Yo Han's totally relaxed]
[Officially starting his attack]
Oh, whoa, whoa!
Wow, but Ji Sung's really flexible!
[A closer match than expected]
He's got good balance.
That's right, that's right!
- That's right! Oh!
- Oh!
- He's not down yet! Not yet!
- Oh, wait!
[Wow, his core strength is insane]
[Touched]
You okay?
Yellow card!
[Gotta acknowledge that]
You lived, you lived.
[This is allowed??]
You lived, you lived. It's fine.
[Warning]
Oh, but you can't lift your feet!
- But earlier, he did this!
- He didn't lift his feet.
[The game resumes]
Alright, let's go!
- Now, go!
- Ha! Ha!
[Slap]
[Will he overcome this crisis again?]
[With his foot off the ground, OUT!]
Okay!
Yo Han wins!
Okay, DAWN. Come this way.
I looked way too pathetic…
[Round 2]
I think you should step back a bit.
[Yo Han VS DAWN]
You have to step back a bit. Right.
[Whining]
How am I supposed to beat Yo Han?
Alright, bring your legs in closer.
[Will Yo Han take the win?]
Put your feet together! Ready!
[Round 2]
Start!!
[A full-on attack from the start]
[Counterattacking in a weird pose]
[He's tipping over…!]
[Out immediately]
[Yo Han takes an easy WIN]
I knew he was gonna win! I knew it!
[DAWN and Ji Sung, go make the ramyeon]
Team Yo Han and Lee Teuk wins!
Hey, great job.
- Good job, good job.
- Okay, you two!
[Ramyeon Cooking Team heads out]
Please take care of our ramyeon.
- Yes, one each.
- Oh! The order!
- What do you want?
- What are you gonna eat?
What were our options?
Just pick one from your team
and one from our team.
[Shin Dong's Pick: Buldak Ramyeon]
I'll go with Buldak Ramyeon.
Then…
- Chapagetti.
- There's Omori Kimchi Stew Ramyeon too.
- Oh, let's eat the Omori!
- The Omori is mine, though!
[Kimchi stew ramyeon!]
You're gonna eat it anyway.
- Oh? Minus points?
- No, why, why?
- Hold on a second!
- What are you gonna do?
- I'm just checking.
- Are you eating the Omori or not?
- No, I'm just checking!
- Yeah, it belongs to your team.
- Yeah, so originally…
- I want some soup though...
[Recommending something else]
You said you'd eat the Buldak.
I picked the Buldak already.
- Eat the Omori.
- I want the Omori.
[Decided on the Kimchi stew ramyeon]
Omori, okay! Omori!
- Buldak and Omori?
- Yeah, Buldak and Omori.
[That's mine...]
[Also ordered stir-fried Kimchi]
And one stir-fried Kimchi.
Oh, stir-fried Kimchi sounds great!
Johnny, do you like it a bit salty?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Wow, I'm going again.
[Lol]
- Are you okay, Ji Sung?
- As I'm walking,
so many rocks are
getting under my feet in my sandals.
[Restaurant / Pool]
[Making the long trip]
[back and forth for the second time already]
[After chit-chatting along the way]
It's really cold, right?
My MBTI's INFP.
The famous INFP.
[They arrive at the restaurant]
[Ramyeon Order List]
[Taking care of the Kimchi
stew ramyeon Johnny picked]
[Casually tapping out
the seasoning powder packet]
[And dumping it into the ramyeon]
Should we add this?
[Spicy stir-fried noodles]
[Carefully preparing Shin Dong's ramyeon too]
[Ramyeon delivery is on the way]
I feel it might get a bit soggy though.
[Let's hurry before it gets soggy]
[Gathering by the beach like a youth movie]
Here comes the ramyeon!
[Speaking like a gangster movie]
It's made perfectly for you, boss!
Oh, let's see how well you made it!
- Let me try it.
- It's made to perfection.
Hey, you even drained the water!
[Prepped perfectly to dig right in]
- I drained it all out!
- Amazing! Wow!
- This is insane!
- It looks so good…
This is crazy! I'm gonna try it now.
[Mouthwatering just looking at it]
Wow, this is crazy.
[Looks so tasty]
Wow! This is crazy!
[So jealous...]
That looks delicious.
Wow, the smell!
The wind's blowing it this way!
Can I use these chopsticks?
Oh, hey!
[Slurping without hesitation]
[This looks insanely good]
Wow, that looks so good.
It even sounds so delicious.
[Now this is what I'm talking about]
Can I also get a pair of chopsticks?
- This is seriously good!
- Just one bite!
[Please, just one bite]
Just one bite!
- Just one bite!
- This is seriously tasty.
[Slurp]
[Sluuuurp]
- Wow!
- How does it taste?
[The taste of ramyeon by the beach]
Eating ramyeon next to the beach is the best.
Can't we experience it too?
[Ignoring]
Let's try the Omori stew ramyeon too.
Oh, the Omori's mine…
[But it's mine...]
The Omori's mine…
[WOW]
Whoa!
This is insane!
- Wow!
- Look at the visuals!
[Whining]
Omori, Omori, that's mine…
Wow, the Kimchi here…!
- This is incredible.
- That's mine…
- Wow!
- Let me try the broth.
When I'm missing Omori…
Wow!!!
Omori?
[It's been about a week, including flight time]
Wow!!!
[How long has it been since having Korean food?]
Hey, it's Omori, it's Omori!
Omori!
(Can't hear)
Omori! Omori! I hope you're doing well!
Mother! Mother?
[Passing the Kimchi stew ramyeon]
Omori!
- Wow, this is insane!
- Wow!
This is so good
I don't know what to do.
This is seriously so good…
It's my first time trying this.
- Really? This is so good.
- Can't we experience it together?
Try the broth together too…
The Kimchi… With the Kimchi…
Let's experience it together!
[Salivating]
[The paupers are super starved]
[Attention, paupers]
Alright, you four!
- This is so good.
- I'm seriously hungry.
- There's not much left.
- Yes.
[A loyalty game with the ramyeon?]
We'll do Rock-Paper-Scissors.
- Ugh, the loyalty game!
- We'll play the loyalty game.
[Already expecting zero loyalty]
Ugh, this loyalty game…
- Okay, Rock-Paper-Scissors!
- Shoot!
Shoot or lose!
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Rock / Scissors]
[Scissors / Paper]
[A match that doesn't end easily]
Rock-Paper-Scissors! Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Scissors / Rock / Rock / Scissors]
[Joy / Sorrow / Sorrow / Joy]
Yeah!
[Battle for 1st place]
Omori!
Let's see who'll go first.
- Omori, are you doing well?
- Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Scissors / Scissors]
[Rock / Paper]
[DAWN takes 1st place]
Wow, DAWN!
[The spicy fried noodles are handed to 1st place]
1st place goes first.
- No, but…
- That's right.
- DAWN's got loyalty for sure.
- One bite is not enough.
[Pressure]
Wow, this Omori is the best.
[All eyes on DAWN]
[Next up and very nervous]
[Stirring around]
This is meaningless.
[Nom]
Is that it? No way?
[Claimed he'll lose his "light eater" title]
Just one bite… Next is 2nd place.
- But this is really good.
- It's one bite.
- Can I have one more bite?
- No!
Just one more bite.
Nope.
[Second in line: Yo Han]
Pass it to 2nd place.
[Oh right! Didn't choose who's 3rd]
Who's 3rd, who's 3rd?
Play Rock-Paper-Scissors.
Shoot or lose!
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Win / Lose]
- Wow. - 3rd place.
[Please, little bro]
[Been losing all day]
I'm really…
[Hesitating...]
Hurry it up!
[A modest bite]
(Staring intently...)
There's still a bit left!
Mmm! Wow, this is so good.
Ji Sung, do you like this?
I like everything...
Oh, really?
But…!
Go ahead.
I… I like it a lot.
You like it a lot?
Do you prefer this,
or the Kimchi ramyeon?
- I... really love this one
- Oh, really?
[I see...]
- Oh, this one…
- How much is left??
- Let's take a look.
- Just one bite.
- Aw.
- Show it. Show it to the camera.
There's this much left.
[This much of the ramyeon is left]
I'm curious to see how much
Lee Teuk cares about his little brother.
I have a reputation
for having zero loyalty, though.
Didn't you know Ji Sung back when
he was in elementary or middle school?
Yeah, that's right.
What am I supposed to
do about this?
- Ji Sung, what should I do?
- Was it 10 years ago?
Back then, Lee Teuk and Shin Dong…
We really had fun
shooting "NCT LIFE" together.
- Yeah, we filmed it in Gapyeong. Right.
- For real, back then…
I'm tearing up!
I'm not sure what it is, but I'm tearing up.
[Do you remember…?]
I was 15 back then.
Is it really good?
Hey, how does it taste?
[I trust you, Lee Teuk]
Oh, Lee Teuk's dividing it.
- He's at least dividing it up.
- But this is really delicious.
[Hands tightly clasped...]
Yeah, he's dividing it up.
Yeah.
Just this much then?
- Just this much. Just this.
- Yeah.
[Lee Teuk…]
Wow, he's not showing
how much he's eating.
[In the zone]
Huh?
- I left some.
- Oh, there's some left! There's some left.
There's some left, Ji Sung! Here!
[How much could possibly be left???]
Oh, you can't even see it!
- You can't even see it!
- But he really left a lot!
Hey, show us! Show us!
He really left so much!
[One strand]
[His loyalty is on another level]
[Sorry...]
Lee Teuk…
[Lee Teuk's empty heart]
This is how much he thinks of Ji Sung.
Just one strand.
Oh, it's so spicy!
[Whining about the spice]
Oh, this is so spicy!
- It's so spicy!
- Isn't it delicious?
- It's so delicious!
- Isn't it so delicious?
[Nom...]
It was hard to endure it too.
[One more round for the Kimchi stew ramyeon]
Okay, we're doing it with the Omori!
I'll make sure Ji Sung
gets his share of the Omori!
Wow, there's not much left for the Omori.
- Okay, Rock-Paper-Scissors!
- Let's go!
- Shoot or lose! Rock-Paper-Scissors!
- Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Lee Teuk and Yo Han win]
Wow!
1st place! 1st place!
[Seriously can't even win once]
Wow, if Lee Teuk's first, you're in trouble.
Shoot or lose! Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Rock / Paper]
[Lee Teuk takes 1st place]
Oh!!
- Omori! Are you doing well?
- Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Omori's mine, though.
[After desperately longing for it]
You're gonna eat it anyway.
Omori! Omori!
I hope you're doing well!
[He finally got it in his hands]
This is definitely my Omori!
Alright, please give him a pair of chopsticks.
[The chopsticks are handed over to him]
Alright, the Omori.
- It's just one bite.
- One bite only.
[And the Kimchi stew ramyeon]
[Grinning]
Wow, but there's a lot!
- There's surprisingly a lot in there.
- Yeah, this is so much!
[Scraping it all up]
Aren't you scooping up a little too much?
No, wait up.
- You said you'd save some for Ji Sung this time.
- He's scooping it all up!
- Just wait!
- He's already drooling!
[Ji Sung has long been forgotten]
[Excited]
Do we have a spoon????
Oh, spoons are banned.
- Spoons are banned?
- Spoons are banned.
[Squeezing out every last bit]
[Full of determination]
Alright, here we go!
- 1, 2, 3!
- His face is already full of mischief!
[Sluuuuurp]
[Moved]
Wow, he's so cruel!
There's some left!
[Seriously so wrong, so wrong]
You're so mean!
- There's some left!
- Wow, seriously!
Lee Teuk, I had no idea
you were this greedy.
[So shameless]
- As for me…!
- Yes.
- You know, I ate a lot of the Buldak one.
- Yes, yes.
Since I ate a lot…
[Yo Han, you won't betray me, right…?]
- Just a little bit.
- Yes, just a little bit.
He's gathering up a lot.
A lot of something.
(Spotted Ji Sung)
Oh, Ji Sung…!
[Yo Han, don't forget me]
Oh, okay, okay.
[He just inhales it????]
Oh, he stopped.
- Okay! Oh!
- I only drank the broth.
- Oh, there's some left!
- Wow!
There's still a lot left.
I'm fine! Ji Sung, you can eat it all!
If you guys leave so much,
what does that make me?
- A bad person.
Oh, what should I do…?
- It's only funny if you eat it all.
- The broth is so good.
It's only funny if you eat it all.
(Can I really eat it all?)
[Torn between instinct and conscience]
He's torn! He's torn!
- Ji Sung.
- Don't worry.
[Bad person]
Go with your human instincts!
I'll…I'll leave you some, DAWN.
Yeah, you should still leave him some.
You end up scraping at it.
- You scrape at it even if there's nothing.
- You end up scraping at it.
[He finally starts eating]
Oh, he's leaving some! He's leaving some!
[Huh? He's still eating...?]
Huh? Huh?
His chopsticks went back and forth 4 times.
Wasn't it just one bite?
[Let's look]
Check if there's any left!
Wow, Ji Sung…
He left scraps for me…
[Ji Sung chose instinct]
Oh, he left a lot!
This is exactly how
I gave my dog her food.
From what I felt, he was gonna
finish it off, but left some behind.
[The sun sets before long…]
[Johnny spots the sunset]
Wow, it's got a soft orange glow, everyone!
This sunset is seriously gorgeous...
[The crimson sun dyes the sea]
This view is just stunning right now.
But I think my face
will definitely end up sunburned.
[The perfect way
to enjoy an Egyptian sunset]
[Lathering up nicely until the sun sets]
[This feels amazing…!]
It really is nice.
Alright everyone,
time for an urgent announcement!
Forget all the points
you've gotten so far!
Your Highness, what are you talking about?
I got my butt kicked!
[Score Reset]
Forget the scores you got up until now.
From now on, through some games,
[Mini games with a status upgrade on the line]
you'll get a chance for a status upgrade today!
So what exactly is this "status upgrade"?
[Prince Shin Dong's & Prince Johnny's quarters]
There are two rooms right now.
But the four of you
sleeping outside is something
- we can't get behind.
- The tent is too small, too.
- So, we'll pick two people…
- Yes, oh!
and we'll add an extra bed in our rooms.
We'll give you a chance
to sleep in there with us.
You won't be a prince,
- but below that.
- A commoner below that.
[A chance to upgrade to commoner status!!]
A commoner level!
- Around a commoner level.
- Oh, a commoner sounds good.
We've prepared 4 games to start with.
The first person to get 2 wins
will escape being a pauper! Got it?
"We need to put something
on the line so the paupers will try hard."
[The two princes, Shin Dong and Johnny,
thought to themselves]
What kind of fun games are there?
It might be fun to play
old-school-style games too.
Should we write down some games
and then choose randomly?
[A 2nd meeting with the production team]
We're thinking of doing it that way at the end.
We thought it'd be fun to play games
and save two people.
Whether it's written on paper or on chopsticks,
so they can pick them randomly.
Since this was my first chance
to escape being a pauper,
I knew I had to give it my all!
I just had to do it!
I loved it!
[Today's Mini Game]
[Paupers' Talent Show]
[Today's Game]
The first game will be the Apartment Game!
[Going beyond K-drinking games,]
APT. APT.
[the game that caused a global phenomenon]
[After randomly stacking both hands,]
13th floor! You know, right?
[move the hand at the bottom to the top]
The person who falls on the number!
[Land on the number that's called and you're out!]
The one who falls on it!
The last person standing gets 1 point.
The last person gets 1 point.
[Must avoid the apartment floor that's called!]
If you get caught on the number, you're out!
- Oh, if you get caught, you're out. Okay!
- Got it?
[Emphasizing once more]
The last person remaining gets 1 point.
And then the second game! The Shoe Toss!
[From the starting line, kick your shoe]
You'll kick off your own shoe.
[The person whose shoe lands]
We'll mark a line.
[the closest to the finish line wins!]
The shoe that lands closest to the line wins!
[Over the line, and you're out!]
If it goes over the line, you're out!
Next is the Standing Long Jump!
- Oh, Standing Long Jump.
- Standing Long Jump.
The last game is I Came Alone!
[Matching the number of your turn,]
"I came alone,"
[shout out "I came alone!" "We came as a pair!"]
"We came as a pair," "We came as a trio"…
[The repeating pattern]
1-2-3-3-2-1.
- We'll go in this order.
- Oh, this is hard, this is hard.
- You all got it?
- I'm really bad at things like this.
[Take care of the youngest]
Wrap the towel around Ji Sung. It's cold.
I don't know how to wrap this.
You can't wrap it yourself?
[To raise the youngest,]
Just tie it. Tie the front here.
[it takes a whole village]
And then tuck it in.
- You have to tie it. Tie it.
- Got it, got it!
[Random draw for the first game]
Let's see what the first game will be.
Johnny will draw it!
[Pull]
Alright, the first game is…!
[First game]
It's Apartment!
- Wow!
- Nice!
♪ APT. APT. ♪
[A game that sets a hyped vibe]
♪ APT. APT.
Uh, uh huh uh huh! ♪
[The princes decide which apartment floor]
We'll call out the apartment floor!
[The paupers will]
We'll take turns calling out the floors.
[stack their hands to the intro beat]
You have to put both hands in.
[APT. Round 1]
5, 6, 7, 8!
♪ APT. APT. APT. APT. ♪
♪ APT. APT. ♪
- 1st floor!
1st floor?
- It's me!
- 1st floor!
If you get caught on it, you're out!
Okay, 3 people left!
- The last one standing wins!
- If you get caught, you're eliminated.
- Weren't we supposed to get caught?
- No, you're out.
- You should've told me!
- I did!
When did you say that?!
The last person standing…!
- I said it!
- This is just a practice game.
[Tossed aside]
I told you.
[APT. ROUND 2]
Now, Johnny will call it!
5, 6, 7, 8!
♪ APT. APT. APT. APT. ♪
- 10!
- 10th floor!
[Yo Han gets the 10th-floor-apartment]
[An elaborate ceremony for their eliminated pauper bro]
Alright, down to 2 people!
- Okay, I'll call it now!
- Hey, one more time!
This game's fun!
Let's play it one more time!
[APT. Finals]
5, 6, 7, 8!
♪ APT. APT. APT. APT. ♪
17th floor!
- Oh, like this!
- Heading up to the 17th floor!
1! 2!
3! 4!
5! 6!
[The floors climb higher]
7! 8!
9! 10!
11! 12!
13! 14!
15! 16!
[DAWN's out on the 17th floor!]
- 17! - Out!
[Ji Sung scores 1 point in the first game!]
Ji Sung gets 1 point!
- Hey, this game's fun!
- Hey, this is so fun!
[So close!]
[Objection]
Usually, getting caught is a good thing.
- Right, usually getting caught is a good thing.
- Ji Sung gets 1 point.
- Why didn't you say getting caught equals out?
- I did say it.
[Announced it from the start]
When did you say that?
- I said it at the beginning.
- Oh, really?
[He explained it nicely]
The last person remaining gets 1 point.
If you get caught on the number, you're out!
- Oh, if you get caught, you're out. Okay!
- Got it?
The last person gets 1 point.
Now, the second game! Johnny will pick!
Ji Sung, which one do you want?
The one on the right!
[Random pick:
Chose the chopstick on the far right!]
- Please!
- What is it?
[Second game]
The Shoe Toss!
There's a headwind.
[Mania]
Can't we play Apartment again?
Apartment's fun, right?
Apartment's the best!
[Deciding the shoe-tossing order]
Everyone, let's do Rock-Paper-Scissors for the order.
Shoot or lose!
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
Oh, okay!
- Ji Sung, decide the order!
- Oh, I'm first.
[1st place Ji Sung decides the order]
1st place chooses the order!
Oh okay, then…
- 1st place, you decide it.
- I will…
I will go by age order!
Alright, everyone!
[From youngest to oldest]
Starting with me!
- Oh, you first!
- Let me explain the rules.
If you're on the line, you're out.
[The shoe closest to the line wins]
Whoever's shoe is closest to the line wins.
- Can we go past it?
- If your shoe crosses it, you're out.
- Got it, got it.
- You all got it, right?
It's okay to be on the line?
You can't be on the line.
If you're on the line, you're out!
Oh, really?
But is it better to
go later in the order here?
[Lee Teuk's quick practice]
[The princes set up
the game for the paupers]
- It was a boomerang!
- Hey, this is fun!
Hey Shin Dong, check this out!
[Thanks to the Red Sea breeze,
boomerang slippers are a thing]
[They must get close to the rope line]
We have the rope line here!
Since you have two shoes,
you'll get two chances!
- Oh!
- Oh, two chances each.
[Player 1: Ji Sung]
Here we go!
Ready, start!
- Out!
[Ji Sung is out, just like that]
[You'd think it was a long-distance shoe-toss]
You kicked it ridiculously far.
Oh, but…
Ji Sung, out!
[Just as Ji Sung was about to throw it,]
The wind suddenly stopped blowing.
[the wind suddenly stopped]
Exactly.
- Ji Sung's out! Next round!
- This is so unfair.
Yo Han's up!
[How are Athletic Yo Han's]
Ready!
[shoe-tossing skills?]
Go!
Wait!
(Plop)
Oh, here! Here!
[Yo Han, you seriously belong on variety shows]
Here, here, here!
- No, right here, right here!
- No, my foot got stuck!
- Right here, right here!
- My foot got stuck!
- It's right here!
- Seriously!
[Buried]
Yo Han's so funny! What do I do?
Alright, Yo Han's here.
[Amazingly enough, Yo Han's in 1st place]
You never know. You could get 1st place!
[Just need to pass this point]
You could get 1st place.
[Player 3: DAWN]
Now!
He looks like an eagle.
[Great energy!]
Alright, nice!
- Good, good.
- Here goes DAWN! DAWN!
Here I go!
[Hyah!]
(Zoom)
[Currently 1st place: DAWN]
Right here!
[Nice shoe toss]
Here, here.
- I'll tone down the comedy a bit.
- Yes.
- I'll focus on winning first!
- Sounds good, sounds good!
Then I should go
with a strategic approach.
[Lee Teuk's special toes]
Oh, the toes!
Oh, the toes are good!
Oh, an inside kick! Inside!
[Player 4: Lee Teuk steps up]
Alright, Lee Teuk! Go!
[Focus]
[Shoot!]
[Refreshingly]
Out!
[Whining]
No!
DAWN is currently in 1st place.
[2nd turn: Player 1 Ji Sung goes again]
Alright, everyone gets one more chance.
- Oh, okay.
- Alright.
- I really need to nail this.
- Ji Sung is up!
You can use your right foot, Ji Sung!
- You can use your right foot.
- I'm actually left-footed.
- Oh, you're left-footed.
- I thought we had to use both feet.
[Wiggle, wiggle]
Alright, here's Ji Sung!
- Ji Sung!
- Okay, okay!
Alright, 1, 2!
1, 2, 3!
- Ack! No!!!!!
- Oh!
[Kicked it at full force]
Oh, Ji Sung's out!
[The person who tossed the shoe]
The wind wasn't helping Ji Sung's shoe anyway.
[and even the onlookers are flabbergasted]
But I just kept kicking it wrong.
Oh, this is… Sigh.
[Currently 1st place: DAWN]
Ji Sung, you still have 1 point.
Alright, Yo Han's up!
Yo Han's really fun!
You gotta be gentle. Gentle!
- So jealous.
- Tap.
It's hilarious because he looks like
he'd be great at it, but then he's not.
[Player 2: Yo Han is ready!]
Okay, Yo Han!
Go!
[Focused]
[Yo Han Deer]
[A powerful kick past the line and is eliminated]
Out!
No, like, during practice earlier…
[Only Lee Teuk and DAWN are left]
At this rate, DAWN will get 1st place.
(Currently 1st place: DAWN)
- I should just kick it with ease, no pressure.
- Alright, DAWN's up.
[Player 3: DAWN]
Alright, DAWN's up!
Yes, here I go!
Alright!
(I'm in 1st place right now)
Come on!
[Eased off the power and gave it a soft flick]
[Unfortunately, it slightly crossed the line]
Oh! So close!
If Lee Teuk beats DAWN,
Lee Teuk gets 1 point!
If Lee Teuk loses to DAWN,
DAWN gets 1 point!
From my experience,
if you throw it high, the wind carries it.
So you have to stretch it out
all the way!
When I tried that,
it flew all the way over there.
We need a stinger shot!
- Straight through!
- Right.
[Wobbling]
Whoa, the wind's too strong!
[Final player: Lee Teuk is ready!]
Here we go! Challenge accepted!
[Will he pull off a game-changing
move at the end?]
- Straight through!
Straight through!
[Mixed emotions]
DAWN scores 1 point.
[ROUND 2 of Shoe Toss
DAWN scores 1 point]
[Current score: DAWN 1 / Ji Sung 1]
Okay, DAWN gets 1 point! Everyone, gather up.
- Let's pick the next game.
- APT. APT.
APT. APT.
[The next random game is?]
APT.
Okay, Johnny.
[Third game]
I Came Alone! Okay, the four of you!
Alright, here's what we'll do.
Bba-bba!
Bba! Bba!
Bba-bba-bba!
Bba-bba!
Bbaaa! Bba!
Wait, the intro is too long.
- We have to do the intro!
- It's too long.
[The intro's super important]
You gotta do the intro.
Here we go!
[How to come alone]
By yourself… And then, you get up!
I came alone!
- Raise both hands!
- Oh!
- Okay, it goes 1-2-3-3-2-1.
- Oh, 3-2-1! Okay.
- Got it?
- 1-2-3.
[The practice game starts]
Let's do a practice round.
5, 6, 7, 8!
Bba-bba!
Bba! Bba!
Bba-bba-bba!
Bba-bba!
Bbaaa! Bba!
(1)
I came alone!
(2) (2)
We came as a pair!
(3) (3) (3)
We came as a trio!
[Jumping up and down]
No, wait! This is practice! Practice!
- Practice!
- Practice, practice!
[Happiness index rises when the eldest messes up]
Practice, practice!
- That was a practice, a practice.
- If you do this, you mess up.
Wait.
[Considering the players' skill level]
I think we need one more practice round.
[One more practice round]
Is that okay?
- 1.
- 1-2.
Wow, this is seriously confusing.
This time, Lee Teuk will start.
5, 6, 7, 8!
Bba-bba!
Bba-bba
Bba! Bba!
Bba-bba-bba!
- Bba-bba! Bba-bba
- Starting with Lee Teuk!
Bbaaa! Bba!
(1)
I came alone!
(2) (2)
We came as a pair!
(3) (3) (3)
We came as a trio!
- I came alone!
- It's three! Three!
[You're supposed to come as three…]
It's three next!
[Ji Sung came alone, but Yo Han and Lee Teuk didn't]
It's three! Three! It's three next.
[How can they not even make one round…?]
It's too hard, so we'll change it.
[To make it easier, switching to a 1-2-3-2-1 order]
1-2-3-2-1.
We'll do it as 2-3-2-1-2-3.
- 1-2-3-2-1-2-3.
- Yes.
- Got it?
- Yes!
Oh, I really get it now.
But can we just add
the clip of the intro from earlier?
My throat really hurts.
- I'll speed it up instead.
- Oh, really?
5, 6, 7, 8!
Bba-bba!
Bba! Bba!
Bba-bba-bba!
- Okay, Ji Sung, you go first!
- Bba-bba! Bba-bba!
Bbaaa! Bba!
(1)
I came alone!
(2) (2)
We came as a pair!
(3) (3) (3)
We came as a trio!
- We came…! Six people! Six!
- Fail!
[Late arrival]
We came…! Six people!
- We came…! Six people! Six!
- Fail!
[Yo Han is out for being late]
Get out! You're eliminated!
- You gotta get out.
- Yeah, you're eliminated.
- It's a practice game.
- Nope.
- You gotta get out. Come on.
- Nice.
[Now only three people left]
I need to get points!
Okay. 1-2-3-2-1!
- You have to do 3-2-1.
- It's even more confusing.
1-2-3-2-1,
2-3-2-1.
Okay, here we go.
My knees really hurt.
From all the jumping.
Don't jump. You just need to stand up.
Just stand up, yes.
Let's start with Lee Teuk.
- 5, 6, 7, 8.
- Can the eliminated person sing the intro?
Bba-bba!
Bba! Bba!
Bba-bba-bba!
- Lee Teuk goes first!
- Bba-bba! Bba-bba!
- Bbaaa! Bba!
- Start!
(1)
I came alone!
(2) (2)
We came as a pair!
(3) (3) (3)
We came as a trio!
(2) (2)
I came alone!
[Lee Teuk, who came alone]
[and DAWN, who was a no-show guest]
I came alone!
- Who is it?
- We all got it wrong.
You came as a pair!
[Lee Teuk and DAWN are out]
You two got it wrong.
- Why? Why?
- And so, Ji Sung…
[Ji Sung scores 2 points in total]
you get a status upgrade with 2 points!
[Stayed still and became a commoner!!]
Seriously?
- Ji Sung's status just got upgraded!
- Seriously? This is insane!
He said two people messed up.
I honestly thought I messed up.
I was like, "Oh…"
[Got his status upgraded while spacing out]
"Oh, I won?" And so, I was just…
But actually, I didn't win.
I was given the win.
That moment was seriously… Wow.
I got such a dopamine rush.
[The older members always worried about Pauper Ji Sung]
I feel so bad for Ji Sung. What do I do?
I hoped that I could sleep in a more
comfortable place with Ji Sung today.
I really want Ji Sung to become a prince.
[Just as the older members hoped]
Ji Sung really wanted to be a prince.
[Not a prince, but still]
I really wanted to take care of him.
[Pauper Ji Sung's first status upgrade]
[Ji Sung becomes a commoner]
Ji Sung, you're finally a commoner!
- Finally escaped the pauper life!
- Wow!
[Current status]
Wow, this is legendary.
[Prince]
Nice! This is the best ever.
[Commoner / 1 person]
The best ever.
[Prospective pauper / +1 point / 0 points]
Let's go!
- I have a bad feeling about this…
- Alright, let's do this.
[The next game]
Alright, Johnny, pick one for us!
- Bba-bba!
- APT. APT. APT.
[What will it be?!]
What is it?
- Which one is it?
- What is it?
[Fourth game]
APT.
- ♪ APT. ♪
- ♪ APT. APT. ♪
[APT. is the best]
♪ APT. APT. APT. APT. ♪
For some reason,
shouting the intro hypes me up.
It's like a magic chant.
When you're feeling down, just shout APT.
I had no idea Apartment was this fun of a game.
I wanted to live in that Apartment!
You gotta kick your feet back
and follow each other closely.
Why is this so fun, though?
Anyway, it was super fun.
[The members are extra hyped for the APT. game]
We'll go straight to the game, okay?
- Okay, you three, gather around.
- Oh.
Here we go!
- I'll call out the floor first.
- Let's be here and come over like this!
[An intro meeting]
Let's put our hands in as we come forward!
[The creative juices are flowing]
Okay, okay!
[Even a remake]
Let's sing the middle part too.
♪ APT. APT. APT. APT. ♪
♪ Uh, uh-huh, uh-huh! ♪
[Wow, this is gonna be so exciting]
Oh, okay, okay!
Say "Uh-huh" once, and sing it the second time,
and then we'll go straight to the floor number.
[APT. Round 1]
5, 6, 7, 8!
♪ APT. APT. APT. APT. ♪
♪ Uh, uh-huh, uh-huh! ♪
- 13th floor!
(13)
Hey!!!
[Yo Han eliminated again]
Wow!
Out!
Hold on a second! I'll block DAWN!
- Lee Teuk, please!
- I'll stop him!
Please!
[They must stop DAWN, who's currently in the lead]
- Wait.
- You're my only hope now, Lee Teuk!
[Currently has 1 point]
If DAWN wins here,
DAWN will get a status upgrade!
[Currently has 0 points]
If Lee Teuk wins, we go to the next game.
Are we playing Apartment again?
[Please]
Well, we're playing Apartment now.
- Let's play Apartment.
- You two are playing Apartment.
When we sing "APT.", please dance with us.
I love this dance so much.
[Forget the status upgrade]
We'll add the "Uh-huh" part in the middle.
[44-year-old at peak condition today]
We'll add the "Uh-huh" in.
[Apartment. Finals]
5, 6, 7, 8!
♪ APT. APT. APT. APT. ♪
♪ Uh, uh-huh, uh-huh! ♪
[17th floor]
17!
To 17 we go!
(17)
[Lee Teuk gets the 17th-floor-apartment]
Agh!!!!
And just like that,
[DAWN confirmed as a commoner]
DAWN gets a status upgrade!
[Lee Teuk and Yo Han confirmed as paupers]
No way, no way!
You two are confirmed as paupers!
What is this?
[Lee Teuk and Yo Han, who tried to impress the princes]
I'll go and come back!
- I'll go!
- Anyone who wants to go can go.
[They fell into the water]
- Yo Han's good at swimming.
- So cool!
[They choked on water]
What's going on?
What? What's happening?
[They groveled and sucked up]
Oh, our prince!
This is nice. I love this kind of thing.
I threw my pride in the trash.
[But the scores reset]
Forget all the points you've gotten so far!
What are you talking about?
I worked hard for those points...
Shin Dong should've been stripped of his title!
Right? That was seriously so shady.
- We came as a trio!
- Fail!
[After being eliminated
repeatedly from the games]
[they were finally confirmed as paupers]
Are there any last-minute comebacks?
- No.
- This game doesn't count!
- Why, why?
- No, no, no!
- It's so fun though
[Except the paupers]
[Everyone had a great time]
And that brings us to the end!
To everyone who watched "ALL or NOTHING",
- thank you!
- We're wrapping up already?
For today's last item,
we'll check out the paupers' accommodation.
I'm so cold right now.
Do we even have blankets?
(Commoner)
I'm cold.
[Paupers]
Do we even have blankets?
Our two paupers have
one last jump in the water waiting for them!
Hey, Ji Sung! Why are you
going there all of a sudden?
Our statuses are different now.
The commoners are over here.
Ji Sung and I have spent
a lot of time as paupers together.
My pauper mate Ji Sung has leveled up,
and now he's a commoner,
so I'm happy with that.
Let's play more games.
- I just got super hyped.
- Hey, this is so fun.
- Oh!
- I was super hyped.
Let's not go to places like Egypt.
Let's just go to Korea and play this game.
Which team has this much fun
playing the Apartment game?
It's been so much fun!
Thank you!
We really gave it our all…
- You said you had a bad feeling in the beginning.
- That's right.
[2 Princes, 2 Commoners, 2 Paupers]
It all fell into place.
[With their new statuses,]
I really tried hard.
[they head out to dinner]
[The beautiful sunset fades into the evening]
[Whooooosh]
[The wind blows even harder than during the day]
Whoa, the wind.
This wind is no joke.
[Dinner time in the strong winds]
Oh, the wind is crazy.
There's not a single spot blocked off here.
[Only 4 place settings]
But why are there only 4?
[Paupers]
Yo Han and I don't get any?
Oh, it's that for us… The bread.
We're getting bread…?
Come on… They'll at least give us food.
- It's bread. Dinner is bread.
- No?
[As usual, the paupers get bread]
Right from when you were confirmed as paupers.
Oh, the food is coming.
Hey, let us have some with you…
[One by one, the dishes appear]
[A feast worthy of the final night]
We'll do the seat assignments now.
What seat assignments?
[The paupers too]
Let us have our final feast too!
Alright, starting from the inside,
[Prince / Commoner / Pauper]
it'll be Prince, Commoner, Pauper.
Oh, okay.
[Reseated by status]
This is too much, seriously too much.
- Prince, commoner, pauper, right?
- Ah, I'm really...
Nice, nice! I'm good with it!
[Finally, Ji Sung gets his dinner feast]
Finally, Ji Sung…!
[Bitter]
I tried this during lunch, and they weren't great.
Enjoy your meal! Lee Teuk, you too…
[The pauper's meal is served]
Oh, come on!
You didn't really come dressed
like a pauper, Lee Teuk.
[Plating]
It looks like a hotteok! A hotteok!
[Upgraded from a bag to a plate]
Thank you for this food!
Wow!!
[Everyone gets excited as the wood-fired pizza arrives]
Wow, nice!
[The main dish is delivered to the princes' table]
- Thank you! - No, no!
[It's bread, though]
Wait, isn't this ours?
[Not a chance]
Come on, it's not.
[Pizza is just a dream for the paupers]
I want some pizza.
- Hey, the pizza! The pizza is great!
- Wow!
[Super excited]
This pizza is seriously insane!
- Thank you for this food!
- But Lee Teuk, it gets better as you eat it.
- Really?
[Resigned, they start eating]
I honestly couldn't tell what it taste like.
- It's warm.
- It's like Pyeongyang Naengmyeon style!
Hey, it's warm, warm.
[Same table / Different levels of satisfaction]
Hey, the pizza! The pizza!
[The wealth gap right before their eyes]
Being at the same table like this is really…
Lee Teuk, from earlier…
I remember he ate all the ramyeon
without leaving any for us.
[Moments ago, during the ramyeon loyalty game]
He's scooping up all the stir-fried Kimchi!
[After carefully gathering and gathering it all]
Alright, here goes his one bite.
- 2, 3!
- His face is already full of mischief!
[Grabs tightly]
Oh, that's it!
[With no loyalty, he ate as much as possible]
[People should live kindly]
Can you at least put that pizza sauce on here?
[Chomp]
[The pizza disappears in one bite]
[Nice]
Mmm!
Wow, this bread
is seriously delicious.
I want pizza so much right now…
Oh, this is nice!
[A cruel moment for the pizza lover]
I'm really the pizza king. I love hamburgers too.
[Munch]
[Lip smacking…]
Hey, what is this?
[Fried squid]
I think it's calamari.
Can I touch it just once?
[Grab]
No, why? Come on!
[Remove your filthy hands!]
Hey, come on! Why are you being like that?
(Nom)
I can at least touch it…
[Lingering sadness...]
So yummy, so yummy.
Just let us dip this in the sauce a little bit.
[Desperately begging for the sauce]
Just let us dip it in the sauce a little bit.
[We humbly request some sauce]
Can we just dip it in the sauce?
Please give us some sauce.
[The princes' mercy]
Alright, you can dip it in the sauce.
[Sauce granted]
The sauce.
[Prepared the bread right away]
But the sauce is delicious.
[Quickly grabbed a piece]
This sauce is seriously good.
Oh, hey, Lee Teuk!
[His sneaky move got caught]
Lee Teuk, hey!
- What are you doing?
- Just give me one.
[Dip, dip]
Come on, Lee Teuk. What are you doing?
[Settling for the sauce + bread]
But the sauce is tasty.
Roar!
[The happy taste of a higher status]
[Moved]
Wow, this sauce is really good.
[Going for a 2nd attempt right away]
2nd attempt?
[Careful]
[Just then, the wind blows powerfully]
Whoa! Hey, it's shaking here.
[Shaking]
The wind…! Whoa!
What, where did it go?
[Now!]
[Stuff]
[His sneaky move is successful]
Are the cats okay? It's super windy.
[Crunch]
[Honest reaction]
Hey, this is seriously good.
I feel like you had something else, though?
- Huh?
- What?
[Denying it]
I didn't eat it.
[Something's crunchy, though…?]
Why is something crunching in your mouth?
I chewed on some sand…
Oh, that's sand? I see.
- So you ate sand, right?
- Yes, sand. Sand!
Because the wind's picking up.
[Looking extra pitiful with his hair flying everywhere]
The sand is blowing right in.
That's weird.
Wow, but this is really delicious.
[Fried squid]
- But this is really good! - Right?
Oh, leave me some!
- This one?
- Yes.
- There aren't that many.
- Is this squid?
- Yes!
- It's squid!
How do you know, Lee Teuk?
[…?! LOL]
Oh.
- Oh, Lee Teuk?
- No, like…
[Author of Lee Teuk's Special Meal]
I cook a lot, so I know when I see it.
You scared me.
- Ugh! It looks so delicious!!!
- Hey Ji Sung.
[Making up for all the food he's missed]
I didn't know Ji Sung's mouth was this big.
[Whoosh]
Something's flying around!
Something's flying around here!
I thought it was a pigeon…
[Whoosh]
[His hair is looking unusually pitiful]
We're gonna need that later.
But is this shot actually okay?
The people watching this right now…
Won't they think all 6 of us are paupers?
DAWN must be curious about the bread.
[The only one with no pauper experience]
Yeah, I am kind of curious.
- Try one.
- Try one, DAWN!
- Then, let's trade! Let's trade!
- It's surprisingly not that bad.
[We got him!]
If you try one, you have to trade!
What do you want to trade with?
- Pizza!!
- Pizza?
[A generous bread-for-pizza trade]
Okay, one slice of pizza.
I want pepperoni!
- Pepperoni?
- Yeah!
[Even paupers have their preferences]
Oh, you're asking for way too much.
So shameless!
[Graciously giving 2 pieces of bread]
Here, I'll give you 2 pieces.
Please take care of my younger brother too.
- Can you give me a slice too?
- Okay.
Hot sauce?
[And he asks for hot sauce, too]
[Bowing respectfully before the sacred pizza]
Wow, then you've only been a pauper once?
[Why does he look so pitiful…?]
Lee Teuk! Eat it comfortably!
[My topping...]
Like the wind…
We won't take it away!
[I'll protect you so you don't fly away]
The wind is so strong.
Lee Teuk, sorry to bother you,
but you're blocking our cameras.
[Sliding down]
Our cameras can't film us right now.
[The hot sauce is here]
The Tabasco sauce is here! Oh, nice.
[Whoosh]
There's lettuce flying in the front.
Oh… No!
The pizza is seriously so good.
Wow!
Wow!!
[Deeply moved]
Wow!
- Why does this taste so good?
- It's super crunchy, right?
- Why are the fries so good?
- Can I try one?
- No.
- Oh, why?
- They're super crispy!
- Oh!! It fell!!
It fell!! It fell!!
- It fell!
- Oh, no!
[Acquired]
It fell!
- No, come on.
- Oh, why?
I'm a pauper!
[Confiscated]
No, I'm gonna eat this.
[He even took that away…]
But I'm a pauper…
If I couldn't see it, I would give up.
But since I could see it…
My eyes keep drifting to it,
and my hands keep reaching for it...
[Survival Strategy: Relentless Begging]
If I kept begging, they might give me something.
How can a prince eat
something off the ground?
It's fine.
[Quick Quiz Break]
Lee Teuk, how many fries am I holding up?
3!!!
How did you know?
[Correct-answer prize: 3 fries]
[I did it, Yo Han]
Wow, Yo Han!
- Can you give me one?
- Oh, sure.
- You eat 2! I'll give you 2!
- Oh, thank you!
[The paupers even share
the smallest pieces with each other]
But this is really delicious. Try some.
It's super crispy.
[Hop]
Whoa!!
[Chomp]
You're really eating well!
It's so tasty.
DAWN's eating more than he has so far.
DAWN is overeating right now.
Why aren't you eating?
I'm full.
- Because of the ramyeon?
- I ate a lot of ramyeon.
You should've saved us some ramyeon!
Everyone, there's ramyeon left!
Oh, right!
Oh, there's ramyeon!!
[Super excited that there's ramyeon left]
We can eat ramyeon in the tent, right?
Give us the rest.
Oh, but…
[They ate Lee Teuk's ramyeon on the beach]
We ate yours earlier, Lee Teuk.
[Ramyeon status]
[Team Shin Dong]
[Spicy stir-fried noodles, Cup ramyeon, spicy ramyeon]
[Team Lee Teuk]
[Kimchi stew ramyeon, spicy stir-fried noodles, jjajang ramyeon]
The Kimchi stew ramyeon was Lee Teuk's?
[Despair]
Oh, then Lee Teuk's done.
I still have mine!
[Give and Take]
Since I gave you the Omori, you should give me the rest!
You ate some too, Lee Teuk.
No, that was for the leftover game.
Mix and cook the jjajang ramyeon and
the spicy stir-fried noodles together and bring it over.
- You want me to make that?
- Yes.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Is there a hierarchy
even among the paupers?
No, no, that's not it.
Why are you looking at me like that?
[Pauper King]
I'm not asking you to cook anything.
[Hehe]
I'm just really sad, that's all.
What else is left over?
- Cup Ramyeon!
- Cup Ramyeon
If you add perilla powder to Cup Ramyeon,
it tastes like pork bone soup.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
But for me, the tastiest combo is
Buldak Ramyeon mixed with Chapagetti!
- Chapagetti?
- Oh, me too!
Thanks, I'll enjoy it.
- I ate way too much Cup Ramyeon back in Korea.
- Thanks for the food.
That sounds so good.
Even if we eat it now…
Don't bring that out yet!
They're all gonna eat it!
[Going crazy]
We were gonna eat that later
just by ourselves!
The production team
seriously can't read the room!
[Cluelessly brought all the leftover ramyeon]
[Kimchi]
Alright, the remaining…
Oh, Kimchi!!!!
[44-year-old in peak condition]
Take it out later! We're gonna eat it in our tent!
[Throwing a tantrum]
Agh!!!
[Merciful princes]
We'll give you a chance to eat it in the tent.
- We won't eat it.
- Oh, you're not eating it?
- Thank you.
- Enjoy it in the tent.
[Snapped out of it]
Thank you.
We brought the remaining cup ramyeon.
- Didn't you say there was Cup Ramyeon?
- There is Cup Ramyeon.
We packed some Cup Ramyeon...
But the Cup Ramyeon's gone!
What?!
- It must've blown away in the wind.
- Who did it?
Who is it
Who ate it...?
A serious incident has happened.
A Cup Ramyeon theft!
- Huh?
- Who is it?
- Seriously?
- Lee Teuk.
- It's someone here.
- If you get caught, there's no mercy.
They said it's someone in here!
- Wow, Lee Teuk, you ate it?
- Wow, this is legendary.
- It's Johnny.
- It's not you?
[The suspects fervently deny it]
It's not me
Hey, why are you suspecting me?
No, what is this?
[No one expected this]
Wait, what is this?
This is seriously so wrong!
[Who is the ramyeon thief...?]
No, no! This judge is invalid!
[It's a night that's very
"ALL or NOTHING" until the end]
- Oh, wait, wait!
- Oh, Lee Teuk!
- Oh, our house!
- No! No!
Will we be okay tomorrow?
[The final day of the trip is already here]
Something feels off.
Leggo! Leggo!
Let's go! Let's go!
[The place where WANGGEOZ arrives is…]
[A submarine]
Is this for real? This is amazing!
[Completely captivated by the Red Sea]
Wow, this is insane!
[The Mermaid Prince's Math Class]
This is the grand finale mission to wrap things up!
- 6 to 0!
- Is this a team challenge?
- It's a team challenge!
- Wow!
Either both the Physical Team
and the Brain Team succeed together,
or everyone fails together!
[Join forces to uncover
the hidden secrets underwater]
[and solve the problems]
- 240 times 9.
[Going back and forth from heaven and hell]
What is this?!
Cheer up, everyone!
[WANGGEOZ's final mission]
I totally lost it right then.
I'm really losing my mind!
[Will we make it back safely?]
We have to pull this off. We have to!
Let's get on the plane!